[{"question":" You want to schedule a cron job to send a message to a Cloud Pub/Sub topic hourly. What do you do?","options":[{"text":"Create a Cloud Function with a target of HTTP","correct":false},{"text":"Create a Cloud Scheduler job with a target of HTTP","correct":false},{"text":"Create a Cloud Function with a target of Cloud Pub/Sub","correct":true},{"text":"Create a Cloud Scheduler job with a target of Cloud Pub/Sub","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You want to set up a managed Apache Spark cluster. Which service do you configure?","options":[{"text":"Cloud Dataprep","correct":false},{"text":"Cloud Composer","correct":false},{"text":"Cloud Dataflow","correct":false},{"text":"Cloud Dataproc","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" GCP Organizations are not available in your GCP project. What type of account are you using?","options":[{"text":"Temporary","correct":false},{"text":"Free Tier","correct":true},{"text":"Local","correct":false},{"text":"Organizational","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What feature do you need to enable to support load balancing and autoscaling managed instance groups for Compute Engine?","options":[{"text":"metadata","correct":false},{"text":"security scans","correct":false},{"text":"network endpoint groups","correct":false},{"text":"health checks","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You are designing an application that will send messages with the MQTT protocol. What service should you use?","options":[{"text":"BigQuery","correct":false},{"text":"Cloud Pub/Sub","correct":true},{"text":"IoT Broker","correct":false},{"text":"Bigtable","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You want to configure services to host a mobile application that uses TensorFlow Lite models. Which services should you use?","options":[{"text":"Cloud Functions and ML Kit","correct":false},{"text":"Firebase and AI Platform jobs","correct":false},{"text":"Firebase and ML Kit","correct":true},{"text":"Cloud Functions and AI Platform jobs","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You need to deploy Redis with unique persistent identities and stable hostnames on GKE. What type of deployment object do you use?","options":[{"text":"GCP deployment","correct":false},{"text":"YAML configuration file","correct":true},{"text":"Python nested template","correct":false},{"text":"stateful set","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You want to try out a machine-learning TensorFlow example notebook with the fewest configuration steps on GCP. What do you do?","options":[{"text":"Upload the notebook to Google Colaboratory. Set the hardware accelerator to use GPU.","correct":false},{"text":"Create a notebook instance with TPU. Upload the notebook to the instance.","correct":true},{"text":"Create a notebook instance with GPU. Upload the notebook to the instance.","correct":false},{"text":"Upload the notebook to Google Colaboratory. Set the hardware accelerator yo use TPU.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" You need to configure a data retention policy for a Cloud Storage bucket to govern how long objects in the bucket must be retained. What feature do you enable?","options":[{"text":"Requester Pays","correct":false},{"text":"Bucket Lock","correct":true},{"text":"Bucket Policy Only","correct":false},{"text":"Encryption Type","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". To be able to configure an existing Cloud Function, what information should you review and from which location?","options":[{"text":"execution time in Cloud Storage logs","correct":false},{"text":"execution time in Stackdriver logs","correct":false},{"text":"text payload in Stackdriver logs","correct":true},{"text":"text payload in Cloud Storage logs","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You need to execute a \"lift and shift\" move with as few steps as possible. Which items do you need to create to accomplish this task, listed in the correct order of creation?","options":[{"text":"1. Create a VPN from GCP to your corporate network. 2. Create a GCP network for the project. 3. Create the VM instances to support the application.","correct":false},{"text":"1. Create a GCP network for the project. 2. Create a VPN from your corporate network to GCP. 3. Create the VM instances to support the application.","correct":false},{"text":"1. Create a GCP network for the project. 2. Create a VPN from GCP to your corporate network. 3. Create the VM instances to support the application.","correct":true},{"text":"1. Create a VPN from your corporate network to GCP. 2. Create a GCP network for the project. 3. Create the VM instances to support the application.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You are concerned about data egress charges for files in a Cloud Storage bucket. What configuration change should you make?","options":[{"text":"Enable Requester Pays on the project.","correct":false},{"text":"Enable Requester Pays on the bucket.","correct":false},{"text":"Change the default storage class from multi-regional to regional.","correct":true},{"text":"Change the default storage class from regional to multi-regional.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You need to troubleshoot an Android app that uses Cloud Storage. Where do you look for logs?","options":[{"text":"Firebase Crashlytics","correct":false},{"text":"Firebase Crashlytics and Stackdriver","correct":true},{"text":"Firebase Testlab and Stackdriver","correct":false},{"text":"Stackdriver","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You want to configure services to be able to perform a regular interactive query of Google AdWords data. What should you do?","options":[{"text":"Plan to use BigQuery. Create a BigQuery data set to hold the data.","correct":false},{"text":"Plan to use Cloud SQL. Enable Cloud SQL Transfer Data API.","correct":false},{"text":"Plan to use Cloud SQL. Create a Cloud SQL Database to hold the data.","correct":false},{"text":"Plan to user BigQuery. Enable BigQuery Transfer Data API.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You want to use GCP-preferred base container images. Where can your users find these images?","options":[{"text":"Docker Hub","correct":false},{"text":"Compute Engine base images","correct":false},{"text":"GCP Marketplace","correct":true},{"text":"Google Kubernetes Engine base images","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You want to set a notification for service spend in GCP. What do you do, and who will be notified?","options":[{"text":"Use the GCP Billing console Budgets section to set a billing alert. The billing admin will be notified if the alert threshold is exceeded.","correct":true},{"text":"Use the GCP Billing console Budgets section to set a billing alert. The organizational admin will be notified if the alert threshold is exceeded.","correct":false},{"text":"Use the GCP Organizational console Budgets section to set a billing alert. The project admin will be notified if the alert threshold is exceeded.","correct":false},{"text":"Use the GCP Organizational console Budgets section to set a billing alert. The organizational admin will be notified if the alert threshold is exceeded.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Cloud SQL supports which two relational databases?","options":[{"text":"Redis and Oracle","correct":false},{"text":"MySQL and Oracle","correct":false},{"text":"Redis and PostgreSQL","correct":false},{"text":"MySQL and PostgreSQL","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You want to try out a machine-learning TensorFlow example notebook with the fewest configuration steps on GCP. What do you do?","options":[{"text":"Create a notebook instance with TPU. Upload the notebook to the instance.","correct":false},{"text":"Create a notebook instance with GPU. Upload the notebook to the instance.","correct":true},{"text":"Upload the notebook to Google Colaboratory. Set the hardware accelerator to use GPU.","correct":false},{"text":"Upload the notebook to Google Colaboratory. Set the hardware accelerator to use TPU.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You want to quickly test a single Docker container image that will start a stateless HTTP service on GCP. Which service do you select to host your container image?","options":[{"text":"Cloud Run","correct":false},{"text":"Cloud Run on Google Kubernetes Engine","correct":false},{"text":"Cloud Functions","correct":false},{"text":"Google Kubernetes Engine","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You want to develop Firebase security rules following Google best practices. Which tool(s) do you use?","options":[{"text":"Firebase Emulator","correct":true},{"text":"Firebase Emulator and GCP Rules Simulator","correct":false},{"text":"GCP policy emulator and Firebase Rules Simulator","correct":false},{"text":"Firebase Emulator and Firebase Rules Simulator","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You want to build an application with conversation interpretation based on machine learning speech understanding. Which service is a best fit for this scenario?","options":[{"text":"Dialogflow","correct":true},{"text":"Natural Language Translation","correct":false},{"text":"Speech API","correct":false},{"text":"AutoML Natural Language","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which service must you enable on your GKE cluster in order to use Cloud Run on Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE)?","options":[{"text":"Stackdriver","correct":true},{"text":"Istio","correct":false},{"text":"Knative","correct":false},{"text":"Spinnaker","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How can you enable clients inside a GKE cluster to be able to contact Pods?","options":[{"text":"Configure the clients to connect via the default cluster IP.","correct":false},{"text":"Configure an external name. Configure the clients to connect via the external name.","correct":false},{"text":"Configure a node port. COnfigure the clients to connect via the node port.","correct":true},{"text":"Configure a load balancer. Configure the clients to connect via the load balancer.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You want to capture the message acknowledgment state of a subscription at a given time. What do you do?","options":[{"text":"Create a Cloud Pub/Sub subscription backup.","correct":false},{"text":"Create a Cloud Pub/Sub subscription topic.","correct":false},{"text":"Create a Cloud Pub/Sub subscription snapshot.","correct":true},{"text":"Create a Cloud Pub/Sub subscription.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You need to set a bucket storage class for data that will be accessed once a month or less. Which type do you select?","options":[{"text":"coldline","correct":false},{"text":"multi-regional","correct":false},{"text":"regional","correct":false},{"text":"nearline","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which command copies a file named test.txt to a Cloud Storage bucket named myBucket?","options":[{"text":"`gcloud cp gs://myBucket test.txt`","correct":false},{"text":"`gsutil cp gs://myBucket test.txt`","correct":false},{"text":"`gcloud cp test.txt gs://myBucket`","correct":false},{"text":"`gsutil cp test.txt gs://myBucket`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which command adds a column family named `cf1` to your Bigtable table named `my-table`?","options":[{"text":"`cbt createfamily cf1 my-table`","correct":false},{"text":"`cbt createfamily my-table cf1`","correct":true},{"text":"`gcloud createfamily cf1 my-table cf1`","correct":false},{"text":"`gcloud createfamily my-table cf1`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which command do you use to connect to a running Compute Engine instance with SSH?","options":[{"text":"`gcloud ssh compute [instance_name] --zone=[zone]`","correct":false},{"text":"`compute ssh connect [instance_name] --zone=[zone]`","correct":false},{"text":"`gcloud compute ssh [instance_name] --zone=[zone]`","correct":true},{"text":"`compute connect ssh [instance_name] --zone=[zone]`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You need to set CORS for some objects in a bucket for a client-side application. What do you do?","options":[{"text":"Segment the objects into two buckets. For the CORS objects, set the CORS policy at the bucket level.","correct":false},{"text":"Segment the objects into two buckets. For the CORS objects, set the CORS policy at the bucket level. Add client-side code to handle the requests.","correct":true},{"text":"Leave the objects in one bucket. Set the CORS policy at the object level.","correct":false},{"text":"Leave the objects in one bucket. Set the CORS policy at the object level. Add client-side code to handle the requests.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". For your application, you are building a CI/CD pipeline that logs information when a message is sent to a queue. Which services should you select?","options":[{"text":"Cloud Functions and Cloud Spanner","correct":false},{"text":"Cloud Functions and Cloud Pub/Sub","correct":true},{"text":"Cloud Run and Cloud Pub/Sub","correct":false},{"text":"Cloud Run and Cloud Spanner","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You need to create instances with identical configurations that cannot be changed. Which Compute Engine feature do yo use?","options":[{"text":"instance templates","correct":true},{"text":"instance groups","correct":false},{"text":"snapshots","correct":false},{"text":"instances","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You want to automatically perform security scans on user-developed containers. Where should you advise your users to host their containers?","options":[{"text":"Google Container Registry","correct":true},{"text":"GitLab","correct":false},{"text":"Artifactory","correct":false},{"text":"Docker Hub","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You need to control incoming and outgoing traffic to a Compute Engine instance. What do yo do?","options":[{"text":"Configure firewall rules.","correct":true},{"text":"Configure VPC Network Peering.","correct":false},{"text":"Configure routes.","correct":false},{"text":"Configure external IP addresses.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which object is a container for GCP services instances?","options":[{"text":"group","correct":false},{"text":"folder","correct":false},{"text":"project","correct":false},{"text":"organization","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is needed to access GCP APIs in your project?","options":[{"text":"GCP VMs","correct":false},{"text":"GCP buckets","correct":false},{"text":"GCP credentials","correct":false},{"text":"GCP users","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which object is used to hold payment information for a GCP project?","options":[{"text":"organization","correct":false},{"text":"billing account","correct":true},{"text":"folder","correct":false},{"text":"payment account","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You need to cache your HTTP and HTTPS static content closer to users, so that you can get faster delivery and reduce serving costs. Which service do you set up?","options":[{"text":"Cloud DNS","correct":false},{"text":"Cloud NAT","correct":false},{"text":"Cloud CDN","correct":true},{"text":"Cloud Load Balancing","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You are designing security for an IoT device application. What best practices should you include in your design?","options":[{"text":"Use a private key for each device. Keep the private key secret.","correct":false},{"text":"Use a public key for each device. Keep the public key secret.","correct":false},{"text":"Use a public private key pair for each device. Keep the public key secret.","correct":false},{"text":"Use a public private key pair for each device. Keep the private key secret.","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". You need to set a WordPress site with high availability on GCP using the fewest steps. What do you do?","options":[{"text":"Configure and launch the WordPress HA deployment template from the GCP Marketplace.","correct":false},{"text":"Configure and launch the WordPress HA deployment template from the WordPress Marketplace.","correct":false},{"text":"Create, configure, and launch a WordPress HA deployment template on Compute Engine.","correct":true},{"text":"Create, configure, and launch a WordPress HA deployment template on Google Kubernetes Engine.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". How do you configure Cloud Build to rebuild your image when a change is made to the source code?","options":[{"text":"Add a Cloud Build trigger, and set it to fire on commit to associate repository.","correct":true},{"text":"Add a Cloud Build function, and set it to fire on commit to associate repository.","correct":false},{"text":"Add a Cloud Build trigger, and set it to fire on commit to associate registry.","correct":false},{"text":"Add a Cloud Build function, and set it to fire on commit to associate registry.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". To be able to decrypt files that were encrypted with a customer-manager key, what conditions must be met?","options":[{"text":"Specify the decryption key with the same name as the encryption key. At least one version of a key with that name must be enabled.","correct":true},{"text":"Specify a decryption key and version with the same name as the encryption key and version. The name key and that version must be enabled.","correct":false},{"text":"Specify the decryption key with the same name as the encryption key. The named key and that version must be enabled.","correct":false},{"text":"Specify a decryption key and version with the same name as the encryption key and version. At least one version of a key with that name must be enabled.","correct":false}],"illustrator":""}]